https://autogen.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
774-233-3000[email protected]About UsWho We Are What We Do Who We Help
Contact Us ** AutoGen COVID-19 Update ** Topbar Nav
Workflows Instrumentation Consumable Kits ResourcesBrochures Case Studies & White Papers Technical Notes MSDS Sheets
News & Events
Privacy PolicyYou are here:HomePrivacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Effective date: March 06, 2019
AutoGen, Inc. (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates the www.autogen.com website (hereinafter referred to as the “Service”).
This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal data when you use our Service and the choices you have associated with that data.
We use your data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, the terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible from www.autogen.com
Definitions
Service
Service is the www.autogen.com website operated by AutoGen, Inc.
Personal Data
Personal Data means data about a living individual who can be identified from those data (or from those and other information either in our possession or likely to come into our possession).
Usage Data
Usage Data is data collected automatically either generated by the use of the Service or from the Service infrastructure itself (for example, the duration of a page visit).
Cookies
Cookies are small files stored on your device (computer or mobile device).
Data Controller
Data Controller means the natural or legal person who (either alone or jointly or in common with other persons) determines the purposes for which and the manner in which any personal information are, or are to be, processed. For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, we are a Data Controller of your Personal Data.
Data Processors (or Service Providers)
Data Processor (or Service Provider) means any natural or legal person who processes the data on behalf of the Data Controller. We may use the services of various Service Providers in order to process your data more effectively.
Data Subject (or User)
Data Subject is any living individual who is using our Service and is the subject of Personal Data.
Information Collection and Use
We collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our Service to you.
Types of Data Collected
Personal Data
While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable
information that can be used to contact or identify you (“Personal Data”). Personally
identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:
We may use your Personal Data to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional
materials and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving
any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or the
instructions provided in any email we send.
Usage Data
We may also collect information on how the Service is accessed and used (“Usage Data”).
This Usage Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol
address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you
visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers
and other diagnostic data.
Tracking Cookies Data
We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and we
hold certain information.
Cookies are files with a small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique
identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Other
tracking technologies are also used such as beacons, tags and scripts to collect and track
information and to improve and analyse our Service.
You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being
sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our
Service.
Examples of Cookies we use:
Session Cookies. We use Session Cookies to operate our Service.
Preference Cookies. We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and
various settings.
Security Cookies. We use Security Cookies for security purposes.
Use of Data
AutoGen, Inc. uses the collected data for various purposes:
To provide and maintain our Service
To notify you about changes to our Service
To allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service when you choose to do
so
To provide customer support
To gather analysis or valuable information so that we can improve our Service
To monitor the usage of our Service
To detect, prevent and address technical issues
To provide you with news, special offers and general information about other goods,
services and events which we offer that are similar to those that you have already
purchased or enquired about unless you have opted not to receive such information
Legal Basis for Processing Personal Data under the General Data Protection
Regulation (GDPR)
If you are from the European Economic Area (EEA), AutoGen, Inc. legal basis for collecting
and using the personal information described in this Privacy Policy depends on the Personal
Data we collect and the specific context in which we collect it.
AutoGen, Inc. may process your Personal Data because:
We need to perform a contract with you
You have given us permission to do so
The processing is in our legitimate interests and it is not overridden by your rights
To comply with the law
Retention of Data
AutoGen, Inc. will retain your Personal Data only for as long as is necessary for the purposes
set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use your Personal Data to the extent
necessary to comply with our legal obligations (for example, if we are required to retain
your data to comply with applicable laws), resolve disputes and enforce our legal
agreements and policies.
AutoGen, Inc. will also retain Usage Data for internal analysis purposes. Usage Data is
generally retained for a shorter period of time, except when this data is used to strengthen
the security or to improve the functionality of our Service, or we are legally obligated to
retain this data for longer periods.
Transfer of Data
Your information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to – and maintained on –
computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental
jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ from those of your jurisdiction.
If you are located outside United States and choose to provide information to us, please note
that we transfer the data, including Personal Data, to United States and process it there.
Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information
represents your agreement to that transfer.
AutoGen, Inc. will take all the steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated
securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data
will take place to an organisation or a country unless there are adequate controls in place
including the security of your data and other personal information.
Disclosure of Data
Disclosure for Law Enforcement
Under certain circumstances, AutoGen, Inc. may be required to disclose your Personal Data
if required to do so by law or in response to valid requests by public authorities (e.g. a court
or a government agency).
Legal Requirements
AutoGen, Inc. may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is
necessary to:
To comply with a legal obligation
To protect and defend the rights or property of AutoGen, Inc.
To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service
To protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public
To protect against legal liability
Security of Data
The security of your data is important to us but remember that no method of transmission
over the Internet or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use
commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its
absolute security.
Our Policy on “Do Not Track” Signals under the California Online Protection Act
(CalOPPA)
We do not support Do Not Track (“DNT”). Do Not Track is a preference you can set in your
web browser to inform websites that you do not want to be tracked.
You can enable or disable Do Not Track by visiting the Preferences or Settings page of your
web browser.
Your Data Protection Rights under the General Data Protection Regulation
(GDPR)
If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA), you have certain data protection
rights. AutoGen, Inc. aims to take reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete or
limit the use of your Personal Data.
If you wish to be informed about what Personal Data we hold about you and if you want it to
be removed from our systems, please contact us.
In certain circumstances, you have the following data protection rights:
The right to access, update or delete the information we have on you.
Whenever made possible, you can access, update or request deletion of your
Personal Data directly within your account settings section. If you are unable to
perform these actions yourself, please contact us to assist you.
The right of rectification. You have the right to have your information rectified if
that information is inaccurate or incomplete.
The right to object. You have the right to object to our processing of your Personal
Data.
The right of restriction. You have the right to request that we restrict the
processing of your personal information.
The right to data portability. You have the right to be provided with a copy of the
information we have on you in a structured, machine-readable and commonly used
format.
The right to withdraw consent. You also have the right to withdraw your consent
at any time where AutoGen, Inc. relied on your consent to process your personal
information.
Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to such requests.
You have the right to complain to a Data Protection Authority about our collection and use
of your Personal Data. For more information, please contact your local data protection
authority in the European Economic Area (EEA).
Service Providers
We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service (“Service
Providers”), provide the Service on our behalf, perform Service-related services or assist us
in analysing how our Service is used.
These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our
behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.
Analytics
We may use third-party Service Providers to monitor and analyse the use of our Service.
Google Analytics
Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports
website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our
Service. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected
data to contextualise and personalise the ads of its own advertising network.
You can opt-out of having made your activity on the Service available to Google
Analytics by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. The add-on
prevents the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js and dc.js) from sharing
information with Google Analytics about visits activity.
For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google
Privacy Terms web page: https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en
Links to Other Sites
Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click a third
party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review
the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.
We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or
practices of any third party sites or services.
Children’s Privacy
Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 18 (“Children”).
We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age
of 18. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Child has provided us
with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal
Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that
information from our servers.
Changes to This Privacy Policy
We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by
posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.
We will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Service, prior to the
change becoming effective and update the “effective date” at the top of this Privacy Policy.
You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this
Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us:
By email: [email protected]
By visiting this page on our website: www.autogen.com/contact
By phone number: 774.233.3000
By mail: 84 October Hill Road, Holliston, MA 01746
Go to Top
